<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hugo Novela</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Hugo Novela</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>hello forestry</title><link>https://example.com/post/hello-forestry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/post/hello-forestry/</guid><description>这是一篇用forestry这个网页写的博客。折腾了很久终于在hugoblog2这个仓里实现了这个功能。
目前在网页端的感觉还行，就是英文实在需要学习一下。
手机端也是可以的，但是具体体验还没完整。
接下来会系统的来研究一下。就目前为止这个方式是最省心的。</description></item><item><title>How Figma changed the way we design at Narative</title><link>https://example.com/post/2017-04-30-how-figma-changed-how-we-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/post/2017-04-30-how-figma-changed-how-we-design/</guid><description>To understand why Figma is the best design tool for our company, you have to understand what we do. As a designer, I’ve been crafting digital experiences for the past ten years, having contributed to the growth of companies such as Hopper, Lightspeed, and Breather, among others. Throughout this journey, I’ve had the opportunity to meet the most talented designers, engineers, growth marketers, and build a world-class team to develop startups worldwide.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus. Donec sed odio dui.
Donec sed odio dui. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue. Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.
Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.</description></item></channel></rss>